hyprbrands.com 2019-08-11

# Privacy Policy - HYPR

**PRIVACY NOTICE**

This Privacy Notice was last updated on July 9,2018. 

This Privacy Notice explains how Mogimo, Inc. (“HYPR” or “we”) collects, uses, and shares personal information when we operate this website and provide our procurement solutions ** _,_** mobile applications and related services (together with the website, the “ **Services** ”) and the choices you have with respect to how your information is used and shared. For information about how we collect, use and share information about influencers and followers for see **Types of Information We Collect** **:**

When you use our Services, we collect personal information about you. This is information that identifies you as an individual or relates to you as an identifiable individual. Below are the types of personal information that we collect:

**Information You Provide Through the Services:**

Account Information: When you sign up for our Services, we ask you for information such as name, email address, company name and payment information. We use Stripe, a third party provider to process the credit card information and only retain the last four digits of the card [correct?].  This information is necessary for us to provide you the Services. If you do not provide this information we would not be able to provide the Services to you.

Communicating with us: When you contact us with inquiries, respond to one of our surveys, register for access to the Services or use certain Services, you provide us with personal information such as your name and email address. Please note that information you provide to us through feedback, surveys, suggestions, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and any other unsolicited submissions without the parts that identify you, will be treated as non-confidential and non-proprietary and we may use it and share it with third parties

Integrating Social Networking Services: You can choose to log in to the Services via a Social Networking Service, such as LinkedIn. To do so you will need to grant us permission to access certain aspects of your profile like your company information and email address. You can revoke this permission through your settings on your social media account. Also, please remember that the manner in which social networking services use, store and disclose your information is governed by the policies of such third parties, and HYPR shall have no liability or responsibility for the privacy practices or other actions of any social networking services that may be enabled within the Service. You may also have the option of posting your Services activities to Social Networking Services when you access content through the Services (for example, you may post to Facebook that you performed an activity on the Service); you acknowledge that if you choose to use this feature, your friends, followers and subscribers on any Social Networking Services you have enabled will be able to view such activity. 

**            Information we automatically collect about you:**

When you use our Services, we or our third party providers use cookies and similar technologies to collect information about your location, your activities on our Services, and information about your device. This is described in more detail in the Section “ **Cookies and Other Technologies** ” below. The information includes

  * Location Information: Information about the country in which you reside. 
  * Activity data: This includes information, such as the time and date of your request; the internet address of your computer; the browser and operating system you are using; the page which you are viewing; and the previous page that you visited (the referrer)
  * Device Information: Information about the device you are using such as, hardware model, operating system, application version number and browser, mobile network information, IP addresses, user names, real names, email addresses and other custom properties. 

                       ** _Cookies and other technologies:_**  

In operating the Services, we or third party services providers use a technology called “cookies.” A cookie is a piece of information that the computer that hosts our Services gives to your browser when you access the Services. Our cookies help provide additional functionality to the Services and help us analyze Services usage more accurately. For instance, our website may set a cookie on your browser that allows you to access the Services without needing to remember and then enter a password more than once during a visit to the website. We allow third party service providers to use cookies or similar technologies to collect information about your browsing activities over time and across different websites following your use of the Services.  We also use local shared objects, also known as Flash cookies, to display content based upon what you view on our site to personalize your visit. Flash cookies are different from browser cookies because of the amount of, type of, and how data is stored. **              **

**_Google Analytics_** : We use Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses cookies to help us analyze how users use the Site and enhance your experience when you use the Service. In order to collect this information, Google Analytics may set cookies on your browser or mobile device, or read cookies that are already there. Google Analytics may also receive information about you from apps you have downloaded, that partner with Google. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to the Services to another application which partners with Google, is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use and the Google Privacy Policy. Please review those and see [http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/](http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/) for information about how Google uses the information provided to Google Analytics and how you can control the information provided to Google. To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you can download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on for Google Analytics which can be found here [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/]

**How we use your information**

We use your information to provide the Services to you, to improve the Services and to tell us about additional services of ours that may be of interest to you.

We process your information for the following purposes as necessary to provide the Services to you and perform our contract with you: 

**To grant you access to the Services:** If you provide personal information in order to obtain access to the Services, we will use your personal information to provide you with access to such services.  

**To communicate with you about your Services and to provide support** : For example, if you contact us by email for a service-related issue, we will use the information you provide to answer your question or resolve your problem. 

We process your information for the following purposes as part of our legitimate interest in the improvement and marketing of our Services as well in the security of our Services. We apply appropriate safeguards to protect your information as described here: 

**To assess usage of our Services**. We, or our third party providers, track your usage of our Services to determine how you use and interact with certain parts of our Services in order to improve and optimize them.

**To Tell You About Other Services That May Interest You:** HYPR and its affiliates may use your information to contact you in the future to tell you about services we believe will be of interest to you. If we do so, each marketing communication we send you will contain instructions permitting you to “opt-out” of receiving future marketing communications. In addition, if at any time you wish not to receive any future marketing communications or you wish to have your name deleted from our mailing lists, please contact us as indicated below. 

**_Benchmarking and Aggregated Personal Information:_** In an ongoing effort to better understand and serve the users of the Services, HYPR often conducts research on its customer demographics, interests, and behavior based on personal information and other information provided to us. This research may be compiled and analyzed on an aggregate basis, and HYPR may share this aggregate data with its affiliates, agents, and business partners. This aggregate information does not identify you personally. HYPR may also disclose aggregated user statistics in order to describe our services to current and prospective business partners, and to other third parties for other lawful purposes.

**How we share your information** **:**

HYPR is not in the business of selling your information. We consider this information to be a vital part of our relationship with you. We share your information with our service providers, in connection with a business transaction, to comply with the law and to protect our legal rights. The legal basis for this is our legitimate interest in providing our services, complying with the law and protecting our rights and those of others. We apply appropriate safeguards for this sharing of your information as described below. 

**Related Companies:** We share your personal information with our related companies (such as with subsidiaries, joint ventures, or affiliates) in the course of our normal business operations and for purposes consistent with this Privacy Notice.

**Business Transfers:** As we develop our business, we might sell or buy businesses or assets. In the event that we enter into, or intend to enter into, a corporate sale, merger, reorganization, dissolution, bankruptcy or liquidation or similar event, your information may be part of the transferred assets.

**Third party service providers:** HYPR, like many businesses, sometimes hires other companies to perform certain business-related functions. Examples of such functions include mailing information, maintaining databases and processing payments. When we employ another entity to perform a function of this nature, we only provide them with the information that they need to perform their specific function. We use Stripe to process your payments. A link to Stripe’s privacy notice is here [https://stripe.com/us/privacy ]. 

**To protect our content and services**. We use your information to prevent potential fraud, abuse or other illegal activities and to enforce our terms and conditions. We also use a variety of technical systems to detect and address anomalous activity and to screen content to prevent abuse, such as spam.

**Legal Requirements:** HYPR may disclose your personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to (i) comply with a legal obligation, (ii) protect and defend the rights or property of HYPR including enforcing our terms of use and other contracts, (iii) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of the Services or the public, or (iv) protect against legal liability.

**With Your Consent** : Apart from the reasons identified above, HYPR may request your permission to share your personal information for a specific purpose. We will notify you and request consent before you provide the personal information or before the personal information you have already provided is shared for such purpose.  You may revoke your consent at any time.

**How Long Do We Keep Your Information?**

We retain your personal information as long as we are providing the Services to you. We retain your personal information after we cease providing Services to you, even if you delete your account, to the extent necessary to fulfill your request (for example, keeping your email address to make sure it’s not on our marketing list), to comply with our legal and regulatory obligations, for the purpose of fraud monitoring, detection and prevention, to comply with our tax, accounting, and financial reporting obligations; or where we are required to retain the data by our contractual commitments to our partners. Where we retain data, we do so in accordance with any limitation periods and records retention obligations that are imposed by applicable law. 

Even if you delete your account and we delete your information from our systems, keep in mind that the deletion by our third party providers may not be immediate and that the deleted information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time. We will securely store any personal information persisting in backup and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible. For any privacy or data-protection-related questions, please write to Operations@hyprbrands.com

**Your Choices with respect to your information**

**Access and update information** **:  **You can access and update the information we hold about you by logging in to your account on the Services.  For instructions on accessing your information, to request a copy of the information we hold about you or to otherwise request assistance with these rights please contact us using the information below.  

**Delete information or delete your account** : can access and update the information we hold about you by logging in to your account on the Services. For instructions on accessing your information or otherwise for assistance with these rights please contact us using the information below.  You may also request that we delete your account by using the contact information below. If you choose to delete your account, we will begin the process of deleting your account from our systems. We will retain your personal information after your account is deleted under the circumstances described in “ **How long do we keep your information** ” above. 

We’ll always try to help you with your request but we can refuse if we believe doing so would have a negative effect on others or the law prevents us.  Also, for your protection, we may need to verify your identity before responding to your request, such as verifying that the email address from which you send the request matches your email address that we have on file. If we no longer need to process personal information about you in order to provide our Services, we will not maintain, acquire or process additional information in order to identify you for the purpose of responding to your request.

**Change your preferences regarding promotional Emails** : You can opt out of receiving e-mails from HYPR by clicking the “unsubscribe” link provide in each e-mail or by contacting us at Operations@hyprbrands.com.  We will continue to send you notifications necessary for the Services related to this e-mail address.   

**Change how cookies collect your information :** On most web browsers, you will find a “help” section on the toolbar. Please refer to this section for information on how to receive notification when you are receiving a new cookie and how to turn cookies off.  Please note that if you disable cookies, certain features of our Services will not be available. Cookie management tools provided by your browser will not remove Flash cookies. Cookies may be deleted by following the directions in the “Cookies” section above.

  *     * For the Chrome web browser, please visit this page from Google: https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/32050
    * For the Internet Explorer web browser, please visit this page from Microsoft: http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835
    * For the Firefox web browser, please visit this page from Mozilla: https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/delete-cookies-remove-info-websites-stored

  * **For the Safari web browser, please visit this page from Apple:[ https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?locale=en_US](https://support.apple.com/kb/PH21411?locale=en_US)**

  * For any other web browser, please visit your web browser’s official web pages.

**Manage Flash cookies:** To learn how to manage privacy and storage settings for Flash cookies click here: [http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118](http://www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html#117118).

**Control how Google Analytics uses your information** :  See http://www.google.com/policies/privacy/partners/ for information about how Google uses the information provided to Google Analytics and how you can control the information provided to Google. To prevent your data from being used by Google Analytics, you can download the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on for Google Analytics which can be found here [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout

**Change your preferences for Social Media Integration** :  You can revoke permission for our Services to receive information from your social networking profile in your social networking service user settings. 

**For EU Individuals: Your Rights under the General Data Protection Regulation**

If EU data protection law applies to our use of your information, you also have the rights explained below. The rights available to you depend on the reason for our use of your information. You can exercise these rights by contacting us at Operations@hyprbrands.com. These rights include:

  * **The right to rectification** : You have the right to ask us to rectify information you think is inaccurate. You also have the right to ask us to complete information you think is incomplete.
  * **The right to restrict processing** : You have the right to ask us to restrict the processing of your information in certain circumstances. For how you can control how your information is used by cookies, or in connection with promotional emails see “your choices” above. 
  * **The right to** **object to processing** : You have the right to object to processing if we process your information because the process is in our legitimate interests. For how you can control how your information is used by cookies, or in connection with promotional emails see “your choices” above. 
  * **The right to** **data portability** : This only applies to information you have given us. You have the right to ask that we transfer the information you gave us from one organization to another, or give it to you.
  * **The right to** **lodge a complaint** **with the supervisory authority**. A list of Supervisory Authorities is available here:  [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm). 

Where the processing of your personal information is based on your previously given consent, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. You may also have the right to object to the processing of personal information on grounds relating to your particular situation.

For your protection, we may need to verify your identity before responding to your request, such as verifying that the email address from which you send the request matches your email address that we have on file. If we no longer need to process personal information about you in order to provide our Services, we will not maintain, acquire or process additional information in order to identify you for the purpose of responding to your request.

If you need further assistance regarding your rights, please contact us using the contact information provided below and we will consider your request in accordance with applicable law. In some cases, our ability to uphold these rights for you may depend upon our obligations to process personal information for security, safety, fraud prevention reasons, compliance with regulatory or legal requirements, or because processing is necessary to deliver the services you have requested. Where this is the case, we will inform you of specific details in response to your request.

**Cross Border Transfers** ** **

HYPR transfers, processes and stores information about you on servers located in a number of countries, including the United States. We also subcontract processing to, or share your information with, third parties located in countries other than your home country.  

In transferring personal information to the United States  and 

processing such information we employ safeguards such as selecting third party vendors carefully, ensuring personal information will be used and disclosed only as set out in this privacy notice and that it is protected by appropriate security safeguards. 

However, US law may not provide the same protection to your information as that given in your country of residence. For example US government entities may have certain rights to access your personal information.  

**Exclusions** **:**

This Privacy Notice does not apply to any personal information collected by HYPR other than personal information collected through the Services. This Privacy Notice shall not apply to any unsolicited information you provide to HYPR through the Services or through any other means. This includes, but is not limited to, information posted to any public areas of the Services, such as forums, any ideas for new products or modifications to existing products, and other unsolicited submissions (collectively, “Unsolicited Information”). All Unsolicited Information, without your identifying information shall be deemed to be non-confidential and HYPR shall be free to reproduce, use, disclose, and distribute such Unsolicited Information to others without limitation or attribution.

**Children** **:**

This website and our services are not intended for individuals under the age of eighteen (18) years. Accordingly, we do not provide services directly to children or proactively collect or share their personal information. If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 16 has provided personal information to us, please contact us using the information below, and we will delete that information from our databases. 

**Links to Other Sites** :

This Privacy Notice applies only to the Services. The Services may contain links to other web sites not operated or controlled by HYPR (the “Third Party Sites”). We have no control over the content, privacy policies, or practices of any Third Party Site. The policies and procedures described here do not apply to the Third Party Sites. The links from the Services do not imply that HYPR endorses or has reviewed the Third Party Sites. You are subject to the policies of Third Party Sites were applicable, and we suggest contacting those sites directly for information on their privacy policies.

**Security** **:**

HYPR takes reasonable steps to protect the personal information provided via the Services from loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, or destruction. However, no Internet or email transmission is ever fully secure or error free. In particular, email sent to or from the Services may not be secure. Therefore, you should take special care in deciding what information you send to us via email. Please keep this in mind when disclosing any personal information to HYPR via the Internet.

**_Do Not Track Disclosure_**

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser. For further details, visit donottrack.us.

**Changes to HYPR’s Privacy Notice** :

The Services and our business may change from time to time. As a result, at times it may be necessary for HYPR to make changes to this Privacy Policy. We will post the changes to this page, and will indicate the date they go into effect. We encourage you to review our Privacy Notice to stay informed.  If we make changes that materially affect your privacy rights we will notify you of the changes by posting a prominent notice on our website or using other methods that we select, such as sending you an email 

**Contacting HYPR** :

To keep your personal information accurate, current, and complete, please contact us as specified below. We will take reasonable steps to update or correct personal information  in our possession that you have previously submitted via the Services.

Please also feel free to contact us if you have any questions about HYPR’s Privacy Notice or the information practices of the Services.

You may contact us as follows: [operations@hyprbrands.com](mailto:operations@hyprbrands.com)

7 World Trade Center, 10th Floor

New York, New York, 10007

Ph: 201-266-0067

**How we use Personal information in our Influencer Platform** : 

_What information do we collect and where do we collect it from?_

**About influencers** : We collect information posted on publicly accessible dot com social media and other publicly accessible websites that are commonly used for self promotion, marketing and publicity purposes. If information is located behind a paywall or a password or have setting that are other than “public”, we will not collect it. We collect: 

  * Profile picture
  * Bio
  * Social media public profile information. 
    * **_Facebook_** : To learn what information is publicly visible on Facebook click the “How is this information shared” section of the Facebook privacy notice here: [https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/previous](https://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/previous) and  here: [https://www.facebook.com/help/203805466323736](https://www.facebook.com/help/203805466323736)
    * **_Instagram_** :  To learn what information is publicly visible on Instagram see the “How is this information shared” section of the Instagram privacy notice here [https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875?helpref=page_content](https://help.instagram.com/519522125107875?helpref=page_content) and also here: [https://www.facebook.com/help/203805466323736](https://www.facebook.com/help/203805466323736)
    * **_Twitter_** : To learn what information is publicly visible on Twitter see the “public information” section of the Twitter privacy notice here: [https://twitter.com/en/privacy](https://twitter.com/en/privacy)
  * The social media handles and public profile information of the followers for each influencer and for a particular post
  * The social media handles and public profile information of who the influencer is following 
  * Location (if this is posted)
  * Email or other contact information (to the extent posted by them on in their name)
  * Website url (if this is posted)
  * Sample of posts posted by the influencer together with 
  * Textimage or video url, number and list of handles of the individuals who reacted (like), commented or shared the post and location data on the post (if this is posted)

**About followers** : _ _ We collect the social media handles and public profile information (click to the “public profile information” bullet above). 

_How do we use the information and what for?_

We collect and analyze the personal information we collect about an influencer to create a profile about such influencer to better understand the areas or populations in which they are most influential and the types of audiences to whom they appeal. 

We collect and analyze the personal information we collect about followers of influencers to help determine areas and populations in which influencers are most influential and the types of audiences to whom they appeal. 

We process this information for our legitimate interest in providing the platform and related services to our customers and for our customers’ legitimate interest in marketing their products.  We implement appropriate safeguards to protect the rights of influencers. For example, influencers can control information we use and share about them as set forth in the [your choices] section of our Privacy Notice, and where our data processing of influencer information is governed by EU data protection laws, influencers also have the rights described in the [EU rights] section of our Privacy Notice.  If you require further information about the balancing test that HYPR has undertaken to justify its reliance on the legitimate interest legal basis under the GDPR, please see [link to contact section above] for further details on how to contact us. 

_Who do we share it with?_

_Influencer information:_

We share a profile of the influencer created by our system with our clients in order to enable them to reach out to the influencers who would be most effective for a marketing or other campaign that they are considering. The profile contains: 

  * Basic identifying information of influencer from their public profiles 
  * Contact information for the influencer (to the extent listed by them or in their name) 
  * Compiled and aggregated information about particular areas and populations with whom the influencer is most influential 

_Follower information_ : 

All follower information is shared only in the aggregate. 

We also share both follower and influencer information as listed in how we share your information- click

**_How do we maintain the information up-to-date and how long do we keep it?_**

In order to facilitate the most effective campaign opportunities for our clients and the influencers we take measures designed to ensure that the information we collect and the analysis we do are accurate and up to date. To this end: 

  * We continuously check each influencer’s source websites and update the profiles on our system. 
  * We apply consistent quality analysis and testing on samples of posts and followers that we use for our analysis. 
  * We employee a team of data scientists that applies algorithms designed to ensure the accuracy of the information.
  * If an influencer contacts us to correct inaccurate information about them, we assess the request and amend the information where appropriate 

_How do we protect the information?_

Our influencer platform database is stored on AWS, which provides robust technical protections for the data. We apply technical and organizational measures to protect this information. For example, we limit access to our database only to specific IP addresses that are under our control and belong to those employees that need to access this information for the performance of their job duties.

_What can you do about how we use your information?_

Influencers and followers whose information is included in our platform have choices in connection with how their information is used as explained in [“your choices”] section of our Privacy Notice.

_What are your rights if you reside in the EU?_

If EU data protection laws apply to you, you are also entitled to the rights listed here section of our Privacy Notice.

_What about information about children?_

The influencers and followers whose information we collect are generally over the age of 18. The websites we use to collect information about influencers and followers are generally limited to individuals over the age of 13. Accordingly, we do not proactively collect or share information about children. If we become aware that we have collected personal information children under the age of 16 without parental or guardian consent we will delete this information. 

If you have reason to believe that a child under the age of 16 has provided personal information to us, please contact us using the information below.

_Cross border transfer of information_

We collect follower and influencer information from dot com websites generally located in the United States and process them in the United States.  To learn about our practices in connection with cross border transfers of information generally see the section above about cross border.
